

# NGO VAN TRUNG

+84 94 612 9294 | trung2601.it@gmail.com | github.com/TrungNgoVan

## **ABOUT ME**

I am Trung, a third-year Mathematics and Computer Science major at VNUHCM - University of Science. I'm enthusiastic about programming and technology, and my focus is on becoming a Software Engineer. Leveraging strong self-study and time management skills, I have gained experience in several real projects to help achieve this goal.

#### **EDUCATION**

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE & MATHEMATICS
University of Science, VNU-HCM
| GPA: 3.3/4 - Semester 6

# **SKILLS**

Language: English (B2)

**Programming:** 

• Language: Python, JavaScript, C/C++, Go

• Framework: Django, ExpressJS

• Knowledge: OOP, DSA, Database, Network

• Database: MongoDB, MySQL, Redis

Object storage: MinIO
 Deployment: Docker
 Project versioning: Git
 API development: Postman

Other:

Communication

Leadership

## **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- 2023
  - Top 20 GDSC HACKATHON VIETNAM 2023 (Role Backend)
- 2022
  - Top 238 Shopee Code League.
  - Top 5 HCMUS Student Competition with ASEAN Information Security
  - Top 10 mentor YOUPRENEUR LAUNCHPAD 2022.
- 2021
  - Champion "Đi tìm thủ lĩnh HCMUS 2021"
- 2018
  - Silver medal at the Informatics Olympiad in Dak Lak province.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## BACKEND INTERN | 09/2023 - Now

- Approi Ltd. Growth Marketing Agency
- Utilize Django for web application development with expertise in Django Rest Framework

## **BACKEND DEVELOPER | 12/2022 - Now**

• Google Developer Student Clubs Chapter HCMUS

# MENTOR | 5/2022 - 8/2022

- Mentor 2 startup projects in Youpreneur Launchpad 2022
- Support ideas, technology tools for project implementation

# **TEACHING ASSISTANT | 2/2022 - 8/2023**

- Kmin Academy Học viện khoa học máy tính
- Basic Javascript, C++, Typescript classes

# MEMBER | 9/2021 - 3/2023

- PiMA Projects in Mathematics and Applications
- Contribute an article about "Dynamic programming" on fanpage

## **PROJECTS**

## Project Student Manager System

- Use C++, knowledge of OOP and data structure
- Basic CRUD app for managing students' info in universities

# **Project Authentication API**

- Use ExpressJS, MongoDB
- Use JWT authentication for user authentication and authorization.
- Use Bcryptjs for password encoding and decoding

# Blog "Sổ tay của Henry"

- Built with Hugo
- · Blog about my algorithm, technology, experience in the field of programming

## <u>Morning Basket</u>

- Role: Backend NodeJS (main)
- Use Javascript, ReactJS, MongoDB
- Use knowledge of authenticate, database, design e-commerce API

## <u>App chat Django</u>

- Role: Backend Python (Django) & Frontend (HTML, CSS)
- Use Python Channel, WebSocket, MySQL
- Use knowledge of restAPI, web-socket connection, design real-time application